{
    "id": "emi",
    "name": "EMI Terminology",
    "description": "So, please check your level of learning in EMI Terminology section !!",
    "passPercentage": "90",
    "mode": "wizard",
    "questions":[
        {
            "id": 1,
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "What does GDSN stand for ?",
            "options": [
                {"id": 1, "text": "Global Data Synchronisation Node"},
                {"id": 2, "text": "Global Data Supplier Network"},
                {"id": 3, "text": "Global Data Synchronisation Network"},
                {"id": 4, "text": "Global Direct Synchronisation Network"}
            ],
            "answer": 3,
            "score": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "Which among the below are benefits of GDSN ?",
            "options": [
                {"id": 1, "text": "Item accuracy"},
                {"id": 2, "text": "Speed to the market"},
                {"id": 3, "text": "Reduced Operational cost"},
                {"id": 4, "text": "All of the above"}
            ],
            "answer": 4,
            "score": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "What are the different Item types used in Walmart ?",
            "options": [
                {"id": 1, "text": "Core Product , Product, Offering, Trade Item, and Shippers"},
                {"id": 2, "text": "DSD, Non Replenishable, Assembly Replenishable and Warehouse  Replenishable"},
                {"id": 3, "text": "Replenishable, Non Replenishable"},
                {"id": 4, "text": "DSD, Assembly, Warehouse, Assortments  and Non Replenishable"}
            ],
            "answer": 2,
            "score": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 4,
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "What are the Item types for 'Non Replenishable' ?",
            "options": [
                {"id": 1, "text": "Item type : 3, 43 & 07"},
                {"id": 2, "text": "Item type : 33, 42 & 47"},
                {"id": 3, "text": "Item type : 32, 40 & 37"},
                {"id": 4, "text": "Item type : 33, 44 & 38"}
            ],
            "answer": 1,
            "score": 1
        },
		    {
            "id": 5,
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "What are the Item types for 'Warehouse Replenishable' ?",
            "options": [
                {"id": 1, "text": "Item type : 3 and 43"},
                {"id": 2, "text": "Item type : 20, 22 & 47"},
                {"id": 3, "text": "Item type : 20, 22, 40 & 42"},
                {"id": 4, "text": "Item type : 33, 44 & 38"}
            ],
            "answer": 3,
            "score": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 6,
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "'12th character' of UPC is the Check digit. True or False ?",
            "options": [
                {"id": 1, "text": "True"},
                {"id": 2, "text": "False"}
            ],
            "answer": 1,
            "score": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 7,
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "Six digit Supplier Number is assigned by  ______ Team of Walmart.",
            "options": [
                {"id": 1, "text": "Buying"},
                {"id": 2, "text": "Replenishment"},
                {"id": 3, "text": "Vendor Master"},
                {"id": 4, "text": "Order Specialist"}
            ],
            "answer": 3,
            "score": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 8,
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "Walmart item number is used to write purchase orders and receive merchandise in to the stores ,track sales and on-hands. True or False ?",
            "options": [
                {"id": 1, "text": "True"},
                {"id": 2, "text": "False"}
            ],
            "answer": 1,
            "score": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 9,
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "Vendor Pack Quantity is the total amount of units in the box that ships from the supplier",
            "options": [
                {"id": 1, "text": "False"},
                {"id": 2, "text": "True"}
            ],
            "answer": 2,
            "score": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 10,
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "What are the different item status ?",
            "options": [
                {"id": 1, "text": "Active, Deleted"},
                {"id": 2, "text": "Active, Inactive and Deleted"},
                {"id": 3, "text": "Active, Inactive"},
                {"id": 4, "text": "None of the above"}
            ],
            "answer": 2,
            "score": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 11,
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "When the CWO flag is set to 'Y', the system will continue the in- bound orders to the DC. True or False ?",
            "options": [
                {"id": 1, "text": "True"},
                {"id": 2, "text": "False"}
            ],
            "answer": 2,
            "score": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 12,
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "When the Expiration date is reached, the system will put the item into inactive status for ________.",
            "options": [
                {"id": 1, "text": "30 days"},
                {"id": 2, "text": "60 days"},
                {"id": 3, "text": "90 days"},
                {"id": 4, "text": "120 days"}
            ],
            "answer": 3,
            "score": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 13,
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "If an item is Purged, which of the following is true?",
            "options": [
                {"id": 1, "text": "It will only be visible in OIF and Store Systems"},
                {"id": 2, "text": "It will only be visible in HOST"},
                {"id": 3, "text": "It will be deleted only from OIF and Store Systems"},
                {"id": 4, "text": "It will no longer be visible in OIF, HOST and Store Systems"}
            ],
            "answer": 4,
            "score": 1
        },
		    {
            "id": 14,
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "The system will not try to purge an inactive item until _____  after the status is changed to inactive.",
            "options": [
                {"id": 1, "text": "13 months"},
                {"id": 2, "text": "30 days"},
                {"id": 3, "text": "13 weeks"},
                {"id": 4, "text": "90 days"}
            ],
            "answer": 1,
            "score": 1
        }

    ]
}
